[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Rachel, what happened that you need to be rescued?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, I need a kidney, so I need to do dialysis.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Coast Guards"]}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What did they do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "LDERETE: They got the Coast Guards and transferred me to another boat, another ship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Yes, she was supposed to come also, but the current -- the water was too choppy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Look, you're smiling in the picture, but I can't imagine you were smiling during this ordeal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "We -- at that time, you know, we were just playing around or whatever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "How long did it take before you got your dialysis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I think they had said eight hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Given what you have been through, $500, a free flight home, a refund for your trip, and a credit for another cruise, does that cut it for you, or is that something that's just not going to really assuage the concerns you have for what you have been through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "$", "CD", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "To me, I'm fine with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$500"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "So what do you think about one of your fellow passengers suing Carnival and saying that she suffered all sorts of damages, from emotional to physical?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, you know, honestly, you know, in spite of what I went through, they were worse than I was.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Carnival"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "And yes, you know, I was suffering a little bit on Monday, and then when I got to my dialysis and was home on Tuesday, but they were the ones who were more, you know, in pain and suffering, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Well, you are an amazing lady.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday", "Tuesday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "And what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Well, actually, they gave us a different bus, so we were on a whole other one, and we had to wait for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "And we've been looking at some of the pictures that you've been taking and the last we just saw of you outside the plane looking like you're having a whole bunch of fun with it -- were there some people who weren't quite as positive as you and were really angry after all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "You know, I think each person on the ship had a different experience, and that caused certain reactions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Do you back her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, I would say I don't know her personally, and if she really went through all that, that sounds like a horrible experience.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "So, somehow you're going to have to get between point A and point B. Are you going to use a vehicle of some sort?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "CC", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, I think I'm going to enjoy the sun a little bit right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Was there ever a moment when you truly did believe this was an extraordinary danger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "We have said this before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "I'm trying to figure out, how did it come to pass that you went from being terrified to being extremely frustrated for a number of days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VBG", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, I think the lack of information initially, they just kept saying it's a little fire.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Tell me what was it like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "The kids had fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "So, characterize for me why some people were upset that the booze started to flow, and other people thought there should have been more?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "I don't think that there should have been more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "It's great you had personal contact with him, but what was said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "All I hear is that these were the most incredible people to handle an emergency, and do you think that's why there are fewer people who are really angry getting off that ship?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "EX", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Absolutely, because you knew you could always find someone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Did you have any idea how many people were watching as you were coming to the end of this ordeal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "As we got service, we started to hear bits of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Are you surprised at the attention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "What was that like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "You know what, that was very interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Will there be a second annual divas cruise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "I think there will be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "How does it feel to be an inspiration for literally people who are disabled the entire world over, as you are now, thanks to the Olympics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Yes, I think it's a massive blessing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "It's like of all the things to choose, why that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Oh, actually, I met him at the Paralympics, and I watched that -- your interview with him and -- and I had a long chat with him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "What did she say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "She was just crying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "And do you understand that argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "I'm actually really good friends with Michael.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "No, it is definitely a debate that needed to be brought up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Are you going to run in Rio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Yes, we're going to -- that's the plan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]